One, two, Karakuri Channel GO! GO!
Today's topic is position shuffling.
What song do you want to perform?
I wanna say again.
Correct.
Why are you so excited?
I'm excited.
I wanna say again.
I want to shuffle the song that was
released in last year's May and
February.
I want to shuffle the costume and dance
together.
I wanna say that there are many simple
dance moves.
So I want to shuffle the song seriously.
It was difficult when you were on the
stage.
How do you feel?
I think I can do it.
I think so, too.
I don't remember it well.
I don't know who will be the winner.
Let's decide the position.
The person who will win the next round.
Who will be the winner?
Thank you for watching!
I'm nervous.
Ready, set, go!
What?
You're doing it, right?
Isn't it amazing?
It's so good.
I saw it.
You saw it, right?
It's your turn.
My turn.
Minami.
Yuzuha.
Misaki.
Yoka.
Claire.
Kira.
Well done.
Is this the only one?
It's amazing.
Really?
It's the opposite.
It was the same last time.
I can't say it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Well, pull it.
It's the same.
It's true.
If you're alone, it's hard to stand up.
It's amazing.
It's true.
Pull it.
I have it.
It's amazing.
Well done.
Shall we change?
Let's change.
Let's jump.
OK.
Let's go.
Ready, set, go!
Yes.
Yay.
It's like this.
We prepared it.
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's interesting.
I can't watch it.
Especially, it's from the members.
Yes.
That's why it feels strange.
Certainly.
Didn't you do it for everyone?
Yes.
You can do it if you do it.
It's fresh.
Yes.
It's a new thing.
Because there is no chance to wear it.
That's right.
From the members.
The main show starts here.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
First, I will watch the video and
remember it.
I will do it.
Yes.
Oh, I'm wrong.
The video is coming out.
It's different.
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Shinme.
Yes.
I don't know this dance.
Oh, no.
Oh, something's coming out.
Yes.
It's the same here.
Let's dance together.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Wow!
It's amazing!
Kurata, you're good at this!
Which one?
I think I have no choice but to do it.
Is this the first time you've seen it?
Do you want to see it again?
Yes, let's do it again.
The first time we saw it.
It's amazing.
I have a crush on you
Ah!
What?
Which one?
Ah!
I'm sorry
Wait, wait
Ah!
Wait
Wow!
Ah!
Good evening
Please come in
Please sing
Ah!
Oh, ah!
Tour, tour
like Peach
What?
what is this?
Please welcome
your passion
We can arrive
from so far
My hair is
which isgeb
In some places
patient
Mia
A
Check
No
continue
Do you fit take?
A
still
It politicians
The
next
in
I comic
lieber
not
keep
Hurry up!
Where is Kiyo-chan?
Where are you?
I'm here!
You're doing it!
Where is Kiyo-chan?
Here!
Here?
Yes!
OK, you need to be careful.
Hey,introduction!!
OK, this position is good.
I'm sorry.
This way?
I don't know.
Where is this?
Wrong.
I'm ready.
I got it.
I'm a little scared.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
You're doing well.
I'll watch.
I'm so scared.
Misaki is in the middle.
I was trying to sing.
You're going to do it, right?
Don't do it.
I'm scared.
I'm going to practice.
Let's go!
It's your own way.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm going to practice.
I remember.
Let's go!
I'm going to practice again.
I'm going to practice.
I have passion!
I hope you have good results.
Members from the fastest people who come
late.
They also например more and more in
Korean music.
This part is difficult.
Chu Chi
Chloe
Play danced
We can't believe she's a player
Can't watching the performance
Sorry
Nose
Wait!
I'm scared.
What should I do?
I can't do it.
Do it from behind.
Yes.
Miihi, you go first.
You're shaking.
I'm scared.
You're scared.
You wanna say?
Say.
Please look back first.
rafU
The loser isilan
gets 1 frame
Sorry
It's not bad
It was nice
I think I can do it
I could sing too
Yuzu-han's face is crazy
How was today?
It was two sessions in total. How was
it?
I think it's cool.
You did your best.
The costumes are different, so it looks
like the person in the costume.
But the inside is different.
It was fun.
I think the Towa-bushi is strong.
It was too strong.
I have to do it.
It's hard.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you for watching.
If you like this video, please subscribe
to the channel and comment.
This time I'm wearing D-HORIC's costume.